What's up? My name is Zach Bailey. I'm filming a testimonial video for Lennart's Group Shoulder
to Shoulder. I've been in the mastermind for a couple months now and it's been extremely
constructive for my entrepreneurial journey. If you've been in business for a while, you've
set goals, you've set ambitious goals, you've set habits, you've set things that you
want to adhere to and follow through on, but it takes it to another level when you
share those things publicly with an ambitious community of guys that are wired the same
way as you and you're actually addressing the habits that you must commit to on a
weekly basis and you're addressing what you did and did not do. You are tracking
your daily and weekly behavior against your monthly and quarterly goals and
you're also able to brainstorm and mastermind with the guys in a group to
actually solve your specific bottleneck and constraint of your business. We do
all of these thought patterns on our own. We're very used to solitude but it
does add a very constructive element to the entrepreneurship journey to be in
a group like this and so I would recommend that you hop on a call with
Lennart and highly consider joining. It's been lovely for my journey and I'm
looking forward to continuing my growth in the group and I think you should as
well.